<!--Marcare un testo plain text di circa 3000 caratteri a
piacere.
inserire prologo XML
marcare la struttura usando gli elementi fin qui descritti in
particolare marcare tutti i paragrafi usando <p> e la
struttura editoriale usando <div>
verificare che sia ben formato con xmllint
salvare il file XML su github-->

<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
    <body>
        <title>Taylor Swift - 1989–2003: childhood and education </title>
        <div>
            <p>
            Taylor Alison Swift was born on December 13, 1989, in West Reading, Pennsylvania. Her father, Scott Kingsley Swift, is a former 
            stockbroker for Merrill Lynch and her mother, Andrea Gardner Swift (née Finlay), is a former homemaker who previously worked as a mutual
            fund marketing executive. Her younger brother, Austin, is an actor. She was named after singer-songwriter James Taylor, and has 
            Scottish and German heritage. Her maternal grandmother, Marjorie Finlay, was an opera singer. 
            </p>
        
            <p>
            Swift spent her early years on a Christmas tree farm that her father had purchased from one of his clients. Swift identifies as a Christian. She attended preschool and kindergarten
            at the Alvernia Montessori School, run by the Bernadine Franciscan sisters, before transferring to The Wyndcroft School. The family 
            moved to a rented house in the suburban town of Wyomissing, Pennsylvania, where Swift attended Wyomissing Area Junior/Senior High School.
            She spent her summers at the beach in Stone Harbor, New Jersey, and performed in a local coffee shop. 
            At age nine, Swift became interested in musical theater and performed in four Berks Youth Theatre Academy productions.
            She also traveled regularly to New York City for vocal and acting lessons.
            </p>
        </div>

        <div>
            <p>
            Swift later shifted her focus toward country music, inspired by Shania Twain's songs, which made her "want to just run around the block
            four times and daydream about everything."She spent weekends performing at local festivals and events.
            After watching a documentary about Faith Hill, Swift felt sure she needed to move to Nashville, Tennessee, to pursue a career in music.
            She traveled with her mother at age eleven to visit Nashville record labels and submitted demo tapes of Dolly Parton and The Chicks 
            karaoke covers. She was rejected, however, because "everyone in that town wanted to do what I wanted to do. So, I kept thinking to 
            myself, I need to figure out a way to be different."
            </p>
        
            <p>
            When Swift was around 12 years olSd, computer repairman and local musician Ronnie Cremer taught her to play guitar. "Kiss Me" by 
            Sixpence None the Richer was the first song Swift learned to play on the guitar. Cremer helped with her first efforts as a songwriter, 
            leading her to write "Lucky You". In 2003, Swift and her parents started working with New York-based talent manager Dan Dymtrow. 
            With his help, Swift modeled for Abercrombie Fitch as part of their "Rising Stars" campaign, had an original song included on a 
            Maybelline compilation CD, and attended meetings with major record labels. After performing original songs at an RCA Records showcase, 
            Swift, then 13 years old, was given an artist development deal and began making frequent trips to Nashville with her mother. 
            To help Swift enter into the country music scene, her father transferred to Merrill Lynch's Nashville office when she was 14 years old, 
            and the family relocated to Hendersonville, Tennessee. Swift initially attended Hendersonville High School before transferring to the 
            Aaron Academy after two years, which better suited her touring schedule through homeschooling. She graduated one year early.
            </p>
        </div>
    </body>
</text>